soundspectrum.com 2017-11-19

# SoundSpectrum -- Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to SoundSpectrum, Inc. (SoundSpectrum). We are committed to keeping your personal information confidential. If you use our services or download our software, please read this Privacy Policy to learn how we handle your personal information.

**Why collect information?**

SoundSpectrum collects and uses your personal information to provide you with easy access to our products and services, and to keep you up to date on the latest product announcements, software updates, special offers, and other information we think you'd like to hear about. This may occasionally include providing you with information from other technology companies about products and services that can add value to your SoundSpectrum products. From time to time, we may also use your personal information to contact you to participate in a market research survey, so that we can gauge customer satisfaction and develop better products.

**Collecting personal information**

We collect information about you in several ways. SoundSpectrum and/or its payment processing service providers (e.g. PayPal, Verisign, etc.) may ask you for contact information and payment information when you purchase our products. We may also ask for contact information when you download software from our site, register a new SoundSpectrum product, correspond with us, ask to be included in an email mailing list, or participate in an online survey. We collect and store the information you provide in a secure database. We do not store credit card numbers that are collected during the purchase of products from our web site.

**Disclosing personal information**

SoundSpectrum works with partners and other technology companies to provide you with valuable products and services. As such, SoundSpectrum may occasionally share your personal contact information with carefully selected partner companies to process partner related purchases and/or to keep you informed about carefully selected SoundSpectrum partner products and services. For example, when you purchase a product from SoundSpectrum, we may work with a partner to collect payment and deliver that product to you. Similarly, when new online music software or services are released, we may work with partner companies to ensure that you're aware of our latest software or services. If you do not want to receive promotional information from SoundSpectrum or these our partner companies, please visit our unsubscribe web page or contact us to update your personal contact preferences. At times we may be required by law or legal process to disclose your personal information. 

We allow third-party companies collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use both personally identifiable information (e.g., your name or electronic email address) and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, etc.) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of Solve Media at www.solvemedia.com, the Digital Advertising Alliance at http://www.aboutads.info/, the Internet Advertising Bureau at http://www.iab.net, or the Network Advertising Initiative at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers of Company who are California residents to request certain information regarding its disclosure of their personally identifiable information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. You may request a list of all of the third parties with whom we share your non-PII by sending an e-mail to privacy@soundspectrum.com and place "California Third Party Disclosure" in the subject line. Please allow up to thirty days for a response.

**Protecting your personal information**

SoundSpectrum and its payment processing service providers safeguard the security of the data you send with physical, electronic, and business procedures. We strongly suggest that you use every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. For example, change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser. 

SoundSpectrum uses industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where payment information is required. To make purchases from SoundSpectrum, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Internet Explorer, FireFox, Safari or Netscape Navigator. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.

**Collecting other personal information**

When you browse SoundSpectrum's website, you are able to do so anonymously. Generally, we don't collect personal information when you browse although your browser, does automatically tell us the type of computer and operating system you are using. 

The SoundSpectrum website may use "cookie" technology to identify your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we may use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us understand which parts of our website are the most popular, where our visitors are going, and how long they spend there. 

In some of our email to you, we may use a "click-through URL." When you click one of these URLs, you may pass through a web server before arriving at the website that is your destination. This allows us to track click-throughs to help us determine your interest in particular topics and to help us improve our customer communication.

**Commitment to privacy**

To make sure your personal information remains confidential, we communicate these privacy guidelines to every SoundSpectrum employee and partner. SoundSpectrum does not knowingly solicit personal information from children or send them requests for personal information. 

SoundSpectrum's website may contains links to other sites. Unless you have been notified otherwise, SoundSpectrum does not share your personal information with those websites and is not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. SoundSpectrum encourages you to learn more about the privacy policies from those companies directly or from their web sites.

The SoundSpectrum Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.
